Help !
Anyone ?
Hello , Michael .
I want to play a game .
So far , in what could loosely be called your life ,
you 've made a living watching others .
Society would call you an informant , a rat , a snitch .
I call you unworthy of the body you possess ,
of the life that you 've been given .
Now we will see if you are willing to look inward
rather than outward ,
to give up the one thing you rely on in order to go on living .
The device around your neck is a death mask .
The mask is on a spring timer .
If you do not locate the key in time ,
the mask will close .
Think of it like a Venus flytrap .
What you are looking at right now is your own body
- not more than two hours ago . - Oh , fuck .
Don 't worry . You 're sound asleep and can 't feel a thing .
Taking into account that you are at a great disadvantage here ,
I am going to give you a hint as to where I 've hidden the key .
So listen carefully .
The hint is this .
It 's right before your eyes .
How much blood will you shed to stay alive , Michael ?
Live or die .
Make your choice .
Who the fuck are you ? Who the fuck are you ?
Who the fuck are you ?
Fuck ! No !
No !
Someone help me !
Oh , fuck !
Do it .
Help me !
Help me ! Please !
Fuck ! What the fuck ?
Please !
No , no , no , no , no , no !
- Excuse me . - Help you ?
I 'm here for Daniel Matthews .
Sign these .
Thanks . Let 's go , Daniel .
Took you long enough .
I 'm sorry I didn 't have it penciled in on my schedule .
- They 're gonna press charges , you know . - Yeah . They 're assholes .
Of course they are . You stole from them .
This works out great for me , though .
Your mother gets to keep custody . I get to take you into custody .
What is it with you ?
What , are you a tough guy 'cause you steal now ?
Please , save me the after-school special .
- Why are you such a cop 24l7 ? - Hey , it 's called being a father .
Trust me , you 're better at being a cop .
I just think I should go back to Mom 's early .
- What did you say ? - What , can you not hear me ?
No , I can 't hear you . Say it again .
- I think I should go back to Mom 's ... - Well , then , go !
Jesus .
Hey , it 's Daniel . Leave a message .
It 's Dad . Sorry about yesterday .
Look , I haven 't heard from you . Would you give me a call , please ?
Daniel .
Oh , sorry , Sarge . I thought you were my son .
Yeah . I 'll be right there .
What do you got ?
County asbestos cleaners were working on a deadline .
One of them finds a body , calls it in .
Says that this whole section 's been abandoned for two years .
We 've spotted people down here , though .
- Who ? - Well , homeless , mostly .
Bunch of kids held a rave in the boiler room about two months back .
- Get an estimate on the time of death ? - Forensics just got here .
But it was the arriving officer who called it in as your buddy .
He wasn 't my buddy . He was an informant .
This officer IDed him just by looking at him ?
Well , he wasn 't positive .
- That 's why I wanted you here . - All right .
Well , let me get a look at his face . I 'll tell you in two seconds if it 's him or not .
Therein lies the problem .
Yeah , it 's Mike .
When were you gonna tell me about that ?
Thought you 'd wanna see it for yourself .
Okay . Well , I saw it .
All right , look . I mean , it 's a little early ,
but so far everything matches Jigsaw 's pattern .
I can see that . What do you want with me ?
All right , let 's just pretend for a second that this is new to us , all right ?
Can you think of anyone that would wanna do this to your guy ?
Well , he 's an informant , Kerry . You want a list of possible suspects ?
Grab a phone book .
Crackhead county punks don 't have engineering degrees .
Now , I 'd say that our cause of death here narrows that list down just a little bit ,
wouldn 't you ?
Sure . And you 're the expert .
Look closer , Detective Matthews .
At what ?
Ask whoever wrote it .
Hello , Michael .
I want to play a game .
So far , in what could loosely be called your life ,
you 've made a living watching others .
You know , you and that guy have a lot in common , Kerry .
- Oh , yeah ? - Yeah .
- You both like playing games with people . - Excuse me ?
Don 't ever pull some shit like that again on me at a crime scene .
- Look , I 'm not the one taunting you . He is . - Doesn 't mean I have to take the bait .
- Besides , I got a full caseload as it is . - A bunch of desk errands and shit work .
Yeah , well , between that , IA breathing down my neck ,
my son 's budding criminal career
and my wife 's fucking divorce lawyers ,
I 'd say my hands are pretty full , wouldn 't you ?
Yeah . Look , I 'm sorry .
I was hoping , maybe , that I could bring you in on this one .
We 're not partners anymore , Kerry .
Hey , forget that we 're not partners .
What about the fact that this guy wrote your fucking name on the wall , huh ?
He asked for you .
It 's not the first time some psychopath called me out .
All right . What about the fact that I 'm asking ?
Can 't help you .
- Wow . - You 're the Jigsaw expert .
When did you stop being a cop ?
Look closer , Detective Matthews .
This guy wrote your fucking name on the wall .
He asked for you .
All right , fellas . Listen up .
These are the best entry points .
They 're the ones with direct street frontage , vehicle access and good cover .
Now , remember , we 're doing this in broad daylight .
We don 't wanna scare any civilians .
Look , I 've been there before . I know the location .
Let 's just bust in there and scare the shit out of anyone
who happens to be inside , okay ?
We 're going in teams of three .
I 'll go with Team Alpha .
Just like the good old days , huh ?
I thought your caseload was big enough as it is .
I 'm just tagging along for the ride .
Go , go , go , go , go .
Check the back . Secure the back .
- Go around . - I got it , I got it .
Alpha Team , I want you in front . Baker , flank the side .
All right , let 's do this .
Go , go , go .
Keep moving , keep moving .
Freeze !
What the fuck ?
Officer down ! Officer down !
The fucking place is wired !
Fuck this ! Baker Team , get in here now !
- All right , go , go ! Go ! - Baker Team , get in now !
Guys .
Talk to me , guys .
Go . Go .
Officer down . Okay .
Stand back .
Move him out . Move him out .
Clear . Clear .
Stand back .
Move out !
Repeat .
Freeze ! Don 't move !
Let me see your hands . I 'm not gonna ask again .
Put your hands where I can see them .
Down on your knees !
- Down on your knees ! - I 'm afraid I can 't do that .
Get him in restraints now .
You have the right to remain silent . You have the right to an attorney .
If you can 't afford one , one will be appointed to you by the City .
He 's clean .
Hey .
Is this close enough ?
Get his ass out of here .
Actually , I will need to remain here
while you deal with your problem , Detective Matthews .
- What problem ? - The problem in that room .
You keep him secure .
Clear .
Shit .
- What ? - I don 't know .
I think that 's my son .
Fuck .
He 's got my son .
What the fuck is that ?
Hey ! Hey ! What the fuck is that ?
It 's your son , Daniel . You remember him , don 't you ?
I know who he is , you piece of shit .
What is he doing on that fucking monitor ?
Well , I haven 't looked at the monitors for some time ,
so it would be hard for me to say ,
but I would imagine that he 's cowering in a corner
with a look on his face ...
- You motherfucker ! - No , Eric . Wait .
You motherfucker ! Where is he ? Where is he ?
Where is he ?
That 's a problem you 're gonna have to solve before it 's too late .
He has about two hours
before the gas creeping into his nervous system
begins to break down his body tissue
and he begins to bleed from every orifice he has .
Oh , yes . There will be blood .
Tell me where he is .
He 's in a safe place .
- Eric . - I need a phone .
- Eric , just listen to me for a second . - Just give me a phone !
- Look , everything about this fits his profile . - I need to be sure .
You 've reached Daniel 's phone . He 's not in right now , but if you 'd leave ...
I 'm sorry .
We have something counting down over here .
Get me bomb squad , now .
Hey .
Hey , wake up .
Can you hear me ?
She 's still breathing .
What is this , house arrest ?
- Are we in jail ? - No .
- This ain 't jail , man . - Oh , yeah ? You done a lot of time ?
Yeah . Too much .
- Somebody open the fucking door ! - I don 't think anybody 's listening .
Damn . What the fuck is this ?
Somebody 's listening .
No .
Those types of cameras don 't have sound .
Fuck !
How do you just wake up in a room and have no idea where you are ?
I guess you never been drunk before .
I 've been drunk . I spent three years at college drunk .
This isn 't drunk . This is kidnapping .
Look , I saw this movie on TV last week .
This guy , he was a reporter , and he goes into this war zone , right ?
He goes in to sleep in his hotel room the first night .
Bam ! He wakes up the next morning , he 's in a cell with no windows and no light .
And he spent nine years in that room .
Nine years ? Man , that 's nothing . Get over it .
What do you mean , " get over it " ?
I mean , stop bitching about it and let 's do something .
- I think we should all just calm down . - Shut up ! Shut up !
I hear something .
What is it ?
It 's ticking . I hear ticking .
Hey , hey , hey . Calm down . Calm down . What 's your name ?
Amanda .
- Where am I ? - I don 't know .
Nobody knows . We all just woke up here like you .
No !
- No ! - No , it 's okay .
- What ? - Fuck !
What ?
What are you looking for ?
What is this ?
Everything you need to know is on this .
Greetings and welcome .
I trust that you are all wondering where you are .
I can assure you that while your location is not important ,
what these walls offer for you is important .
Salvation , if you earn it .
Three hours from now , the door to this house will open .
Unfortunately , you only have two hours to live .
Right now , you are breathing in a deadly nerve agent .
You 've been breathing it since you arrived here .
Those of you familiar with the Tokyo subway attacks
will know its devastating effects on the human body .
The only way to overcome it and walk out that door
is to find an antidote .
Several are hidden around this house .
One is inside the safe in front of you .
You all possess the combination to the safe .
Think hard . The numbers are in the back of your mind .
The clue to their order can be found over the rainbow .
Once you realize what you all have in common ,
you will gain a better understanding of why you 're here .
" X " marks the spot for that clue , so look carefully .
Let the game begin .
- Who is this ? - What does he mean , gas ?
- And how did you know where to find this ? - This is bullshit .
" Do not attempt to use this key on the door to this room " .
Fuck this , man .
- Yeah , fuck this . That 's a good idea . - No , no .
- That 's not a good idea . - So what are we gonna do , huh ?
- Sit here ? - The note said not to use the key .
Who gives a shit about the note , all right ?
This is all a fucking big goddamn joke , and I 'm about to end it .
You better start talking right now .
- What is this ? - It 's a game .
It ain 't no fucking game ! My man just got his head blown off .
- He 's testing us . - Who 's testing us ?
Jigsaw .
- Who the hell is Jigsaw ? - You don 't watch the fucking news ?
- No . Who is he ? - He 's a serial killer .
No , he 's not .
He 's testing us . He wants us to survive this .
But you have to play by the fucking rules !
I 'm gonna ask you again . How do you know all this ?
Because I 've played before .
I want a tech team in here now . Find out where that feed is coming from .
What do you want with me ?
- A little of your time , Detective . - I don 't have any time .
You asked me what I wanted , and I told you .
Believe me when I tell you your son is in a lot of trouble .
And what if I give you a little bit of my time ? What then ?
I only wanna talk to you . Everyone else must leave .
- Those are my conditions . - No . It 's a crime scene . Nobody leaves .
They don 't have to leave the building .
They just have to leave this area long enough for me to talk to you .
If you agree to that , then you will see your son again .
If I don 't see my son again , I swear to God I 'll rip your fucking head off .
I don 't intend to mock you , Officer , but I 'm a cancer patient .
How could you possibly put me in any more pain than I 'm already in ?
Just get them here now .
All right , tech team 's on the way .
Should have your signal traced within an hour , maybe two .
He said he wants to talk to me alone .
- Well , maybe you should talk to him . - Well , fuck that .
Five minutes , old-school method .
He 's not gonna respond to the phone-book treatment . You know that .
Don 't underestimate a tried and true method here .
I am the one who has been working on this case from day one .
I have been spending every waking moment piecing it together .
Maybe that 's why you ain 't got a goddamn family for yourself
and you can 't understand what this man is going through .
- Don 't . - Look ...
I don 't wanna talk to him .
Listen , you already lost your son one time before
because you got involved with me .
It 's not gonna happen again .
This is bullshit .
What are we gonna do ?
Just humor him . Buy us a little more time .
You can win this , Eric . You can beat him .
- Come on . - All right .
... find an antidote .
Several are hidden around this house .
One is inside the safe in front of you .
You all possess the combination to the safe .
Think hard . The numbers are in the back of your mind .
The clue to their order can be found ...
Shit .
Hey , wait a minute . Where you going ?
I 'm gonna find an antidote , and I 'm gonna get out of here .
What ? Antidote ? You been in the joint .
You talked to the guards that run the chambers .
You know there ain 't no antidote for this shit .
Look at this . The doors are locked .
You hear that ? It 's wood .
Plaster . It 's not a fortress . It 's a fucking house .
All I 'm saying is let 's just take our time and come up with a game plan .
Well , you come up with the game plan . All right ? I 'm getting out of here .
Look .
- You okay ? - Yeah , I 'm fine .
I wouldn 't do that if I was you .
You don 't know what 's behind that fucking door .
Fuck .
Shit .
Clear the room .
Okay . Let 's talk .
Sit down , Eric .
I want to play a game .
The rules are simple .
All you have to do is sit here and talk to me ,
listen to me .
If you do that long enough , then you will find your son
in a safe and secure state .
We haven 't been properly introduced . My name 's John .
- I thought you liked to be called Jigsaw . - No , no .
It was the police and the press who coined the nickname Jigsaw .
I never encouraged or claimed that .
The jigsaw piece I cut from my subjects was only ever meant to be a symbol
that that subject was missing something .
A vital piece of the human puzzle . The survival instinct .
This is all really , really interesting , John ,
but right now I 'd really like for you to talk to me ...
I am talking to you .
You 're not listening .
- Don 't forget the rules . - I 'm listening to you ,
but all I 'm hearing is the same sick fucking bullshit
that comes about two seconds into every interview I 've ever done
with one of you fucking people .
Well , that 's an interesting approach to police work , isn 't it ?
Aren 't you supposed to be convincing me that I 'm your friend ,
lulling me into a false sense of security so that I 'll confide in you ?
It 's a little hard to follow the manual when you 've got my son , John .
The manual ?
What do you really wanna do to me right now , huh ?
What would you have done five years ago , huh ?
Would you have followed the manual then ?
Would you have broken my jaw with a flashlight ?
You seem to know a whole lot about me .
I know you were once considered a fearless police officer .
Do you feel a whole lot safer now that you only sit behind a desk ?
I feel a whole lot of things right now .
But you feel alive . That 's what you feel .
And that 's the point .
Would you
kindly get me a glass of water ?
I would very much appreciate that .
Fuck !
Well , we 've established
that the macho-bullshit approach isn 't opening the door .
- Any other suggestions ? - Look who 's talking .
The only door you know how to open is between your legs .
- Why don 't you shut the hell up , all right ? - Come on , man .
- Why don 't you shut the hell up ? - I 'm sick of your bullshit .
- That 's right , back up , bitch ! - You little dickhead .
- Asshole ! - Hey !
What you gonna do ? Yeah , yeah , that 's right , back up !
Okay , man . All right . Nobody take shit from nobody .
We 've established that .
- Did you find anything ? - No . Nothing .
So , that ink on your arm , that 's Joliet , right ?
Yeah . So ?
- Well , I did a stretch there myself . - I 'm proud of you .
And you , what is your correctional facility of choice ?
What 's your point ?
My point is , you didn 't get that way by teaching grade school , right ?
That makes three of us that 's done time .
I think we should be concentrating on that tape ,
'cause that tape said we have more in common than we know .
I say the three of us doing stretches ...
Hey ! I found a door over here .
I need the flashlight .
Over there .
What the fuck ?
Oh , shit !
Hey !
- Damn , kid . - Sorry .
- " Obi " . - What the fuck is a Obi ?
Obi . It 's my name .
Hello , Obi . I want to play a game .
For years , you have burned those around you
with your lies , cons and deceits .
Now you 'll have a chance to redeem yourself
for the games you 've played with others
by playing one of mine .
Inside the device in front of you are two antidotes
for the poison coursing through your veins .
One is my gift to you for helping me kidnap the others .
The second is yours to donate .
However , one of them will come with a price .
Remember , Obi ,
once you are in hell , only the devil can help you out .
Wait a minute . What does that mean , " kidnap the others " ?
- How would I know ? - Because you put us here .
The car .
It was ...
I knew I knew him .
You 're the last person I saw before I woke up here .
You did this .
Are you sure it 's him ? You better be sure .
I 'm sure .
You would have done the same . I did what I had to do .
I 'll give you a choice .
- You got five seconds to get us out of here . - I don 't know the way out .
Bullshit ! You put us in here . You can get us out of here .
No , I can 't .
- Then you 're a dead man . - So are you .
He 's not gonna ... Wait , wait , wait , wait ! Wait , listen to me .
Okay , we got two antidotes at the back of that oven .
- We 're wasting time here . - Wasting time ? Are you kidding me ?
He kidnapped me in the middle of the night .
We don 't even know what 's in those syringes .
You willing to stick yourself in the arm to find out ?
Okay , wait . So who gets them ?
I mean , there 's two . So which two people get the antidote ?
We 'll work that out later !
Right now you 're going in there
or I 'll kill you where you stand .
Shit .
If you 're gonna threaten me with a knife , you may as well cut me a little .
I guess I 'm going in there to get those needles .
But I get one .
- One for me . - Hurry up .
Come on , baby . You guys can fight over this one .
Thank you , Obi .
Come on .
- Oh , shit . The fucking door closed ! - Open the door !
Open the door !
It 's locked . I can 't open it .
Open the fucking door ! Not funny !
Come on ! Get him out of there !
The door !
The nail !
I can 't get it open !
- Get him out of there ! - Not funny !
Use your coat ! Use your fucking coat !
- Come on ! He 's burning up ! - Stop it !
- Come on ! - Turn ! Turn !
Stop it .
- You gotta put your weight on it . - Stop it .
My man 's dying !
Guys , there 's a window over here .
- He 's got the antidote . - Stop it !
Get him out .
- Hurry ! - Get it open .
- Fuck ! - ... glass or something .
- Stop it ! - Hang on , man . We 're gonna get you out .
Shit .
Stop it ! Stop it ! Stop it ! Stop it ! Stop it !
Get out of the fucking way ! Go on , move ! Move !
Here . Shit ! Come on !
The needles !
He ain 't got the fucking needles ! It 's fucking in there !
I want the fucking needles ! I want the fucking needles !
Calm down .
- Fuck ! - The needles are fucking melted .
They 're gone .
He had a choice .
Another one down , Kerry .
How much more time are we gonna waste on this bastard ?
We 're not wasting time .
We 're doing exactly what we should be doing until the tech team gets here .
It 's not what it looks like to me .
You see , Detective , Darwin 's theory of evolution
and survival of the fittest , based on his little trip to the Galápagos ,
no longer applies on this planet .
We have a human race that doesn 't have the edge
or the will to survive .
- What the fuck do you want ? - It 's hard to remain calm , isn 't it ,
when your son is walking around on those monitors ?
I can 't give you what you want if you don 't tell me what the fuck it is .
I told you what it is .
- Just remember the rules . - No , you said you wanted to talk .
Then you said you wanted to play a game . You 're talking , but it means nothing !
What do you think the cure for cancer is , Eric ?
- What ? - The cure for cancer .
- What is it ? - I don 't know what it is ,
but I know it 's not killing and torturing people
for your own sick fucking pleasure .
I 've never murdered anyone in my life . The decisions are up to them .
Yeah , well , putting a gun to someone 's head
and forcing them to pull the trigger is still murder .
Since when is force a problem for you ?
Why are you so desperate to get your son back ?
'Cause he 's my son .
What 's the last thing you said to him before you left him ?
Well , then , go !
Seems to me that the knowledge of your son 's impending death
is causing you to act .
Forgive all his sins , to wipe the slate clean ...
Why is it that we 're only willing to do that when a life is at stake ?
I 've always loved my son . That 's never changed .
No , no . It 's changed now .
You see , the knowledge of death changes everything .
If I were to tell you the exact date and time of your own death ,
it would shatter your world completely .
I know .
Can you imagine what it feels like to have someone sit you down ...
John Kramer .
... and tell you that you 're dying ?
The gravity of that ?
That the clock 's ticking for you .
In a split second , your world is cracked open .
You look at things differently . You smell things differently .
You savor everything , be it a glass of water or a walk in the park .
The clock is ticking , John .
But most people have the luxury
of not knowing when that clock 's gonna go off ,
and the irony of it is that that keeps them from really living their life .
It keeps them sleepwalking .
It keeps them drinking that glass of water , but never really tasting it .
You can still fix this , John .
Yeah , but can we fix you ?
Me ?
I 'm not fixable .
I 've got cancer .
You 're using cancer as an excuse for what you do ?
No .
The cancer isn 't what started me in my work .
It was the moment I decided to end my life
that started me in my work
and brought meaning to it .
Fuck !
I had literally driven myself to suicide ,
and I had failed .
My body had not been strong enough to repel cancer cells ,
yet I had lived through a plunge off a cliff .
But , to my amazement , I was alive .
And I was determined to spend the rest of my days
testing the fabric of human nature .
Do you understand , Eric ?
You got a chance to do something . Do it right now , John .
Just tell me where my son is .
I 'll help you .
I don 't need your help , and I can tell you still don 't understand .
Those who don 't appreciate life do not deserve life .
My son appreciates his life .
But do you appreciate yours ? Do you appreciate your son 's ?
Oh , this is shit !
Don 't forget the rules
if you wanna find your son .
Where are you ?
No . No , we don 't have 15 minutes .
We need that location to the video feed .
Hey . I don 't think we should stop , okay ?
Laura , can you hear me ?
That 's the second time I 've had to wake up in this shithole .
Think you can stand up ?
Yeah , but I don 't really want to .
There 's so much left to do .
So many people left to talk to .
This can 't be it .
It 's not .
- Amanda , you said you survived this , right ? - I what ?
This guy , whoever 's doing it ,
you said that you 've played before and you survived .
Yeah .
So that means we could survive .
Wait . Amanda , why did he pick you ?
Because I was a fucking junkie .
And the funny thing is , I passed his little test .
If you passed his test , then why are you back here ?
I wasn 't being very good to myself .
- How long have you ... - I started in jail .
- What were you arrested for ? - Possession .
But I thought you said that ...
Maybe you should talk to the cop who arrested me .
I 'm guessing you 've never been arrested before .
No .
I mean , I 've been in trouble a few times , you know , in and out of stuff .
My dad 's a ...
He 's a real hardass .
You know , he 's probably got half the city right now looking for me
just so he can kick my ass for disappearing on him .
Yeah .
Probably .
We found a door . Come on .
Come on . We have to go .
It 's the only one without a lock , but we can 't get it open .
- How 's it going ? - It 's stuck on something .
Oh , shit .
- Here , let me try . Move , move ! Come on . - Will you take it easy ? Jesus !
Just back up , all right ?
If it 's stuck , it 's a trap .
Lady , this whole house is a trap .
Obviously someone didn 't want us to get into this room .
- Now what ? - I 'm gonna be right back , okay ?
Whatever we do , we got four minutes to get it done .
Hello , Xavier . I want to play a game .
The game I want to play is very similar
to the one that you 've been playing as a drug dealer .
The game of offering hope to the desperate for a price .
I think we can agree that your situation is desperate .
So I offer you hope .
The price you pay is that you must crawl into the same pit of squalor
you force your customers into .
- By entering this room ... - Oh , my God .
... a timer has been started .
When the timer expires , the door in front of you will be locked forever .
- Only in finding the key ... - Guys ? Guys .
- What ? - Look .
... before the timer runs out can you unlock it
- and retrieve the antidote inside . - Oh , my God .
I will give you just one hint as to where that key is .
It will be like finding a needle in a haystack .
Let the game begin .
Somebody 's going in there .
Now , look , somebody 's fucking going in there , man .
No ! No ! No !
- Oh , shit . - What the fuck are you doing ?
- Stop . - What are you doing ?
- No ! No ! - What the fuck are you doing ?
- No ! No ! Please ! - Let her go now .
No !
Shit !
My God .
Come on !
- We don 't have time ! - Oh , shit .
What the fuck 's wrong with you ?
What are you doing ?
- You 're out of your fucking mind . - Hurry up .
Oh , shit !
Come on !
We don 't have time .
Keep fucking looking .
- Come on ! Come on ! - Fuck you !
What the fuck ?
Somebody 's gotta help her .
What the fuck , guys ?
Fuck !
No . No . No . No .
No !
No . No !
Come on .
No , no , no .
- You fucking bitch ! - All right . That 's enough .
That 's not nearly enough , man .
Stop this bullshit .
Did you hear that tape ?
He knows about us . Our names .
There 's something that we 're not seeing .
Jail .
You said you three had been there .
Make it four .
- For what ? - Doesn 't matter .
Anybody else wanna own up ?
What about you ? You got juvie written all over you .
No , never been .
All right .
- Let 's talk this out . - No .
No more talking .
The only thing you people have in common is holding me back .
I 'm gone .
- Where is this goddamn tech team ? - They 'll be here any second .
I 'm not listening to this anymore .
- Another second is too fucking long . - Look , I know how this guy works , okay ?
He 's playing a game .
Eric just needs to stay in it a little bit longer .
Take a look at the clock .
You need to start thinking outside the box , or his son is gonna end up in one .
His work .
You wanna get to him , that 's how you do it .
I mean , he 's relishing this .
It 's an opportunity to be heard , to be studied .
Threaten to destroy his work .
How will you get your conviction without all this evidence , Eric ?
I don 't need this shit to convict you .
So go ahead . Destroy it .
- I will . - Destroy it all .
Just know it will not save your son if you do .
You kill my son , I kill you .
Go ahead .
Why wait ? We both know the sort of person you are , sir .
- Get out of here . - The sort of person
who guns down an unarmed suspect .
In fact , the sort of person who plants evidence
in order to obtain a conviction .
The sort of person whose wife leaves him and whose son hates him .
Shut the fuck up !
- Okay , set up all the traces to the satellite . - Let 's go .
Your tech team 's arrived .
Just in time .
You better hope they find the source of that feed .
There 's something I haven 't told you , Eric .
I 'm done listening to you .
Maybe I can just show it to you .
But , unfortunately , it 's going to be difficult for me to get it myself ,
so perhaps you could ask the people who are listening on that walkie in there
if they could get it for me , all right ?
Brown desk .
Second drawer down .
You may not remember all those people ,
but I 'm sure they remember you .
You were the arresting officer in all of their cases ,
and you were the one who planted all the evidence
used to obtain their convictions .
You were the one who put them away .
Your son is playing a game
with a lot of people who don 't like you very much , Detective .
It would be a shame if they discovered who he was .
You all possess the combination to the safe .
Think hard . The numbers are in the back of your mind .
The clue to their order can be found over the rainbow .
Son of a bitch .
- What are you doing ? - I haven 't decided yet .
You know , the others , they 're scared of you .
Good .
You and me ,
we can keep going at each other like we 're back in the yard ,
or we can come together and figure out who 's doing this to us .
You and the others can do what you want .
I already found what I 'm looking for .
You remind me of me .
No matter what kind of fucked-up situation you 're in ,
you always gotta find yourself an enemy .
You know what ? I got enemies , man .
Outside these fucking walls , bro .
And they 're looking for me .
And if they don 't find me , they 're going after the ones closest to me .
My family .
You understand ?
No .
I don 't understand .
It 's just me , and that 's the way I like it .
Now , turn around .
- What ? - Turn around .
Oh , shit .
- No . We can 't stop . - Shit .
Oh , my God .
We 've been here for two hours . If what that tape says is true ,
then in one hour , the front door will open .
We 're not gonna make it that long .
That 's a real winning attitude .
She knows what she 's talking about .
Oh , yeah ?
" X " marks the spot .
What ?
" X " marks ...
Marks the spot .
There 's the answer .
What are you doing with him ?
This is your father ?
- What ? You know him ? - Yeah .
He 's the guy who put me away . He set me up .
Tell me that 's not your father .
It 's okay . It 's okay .
I can 't trust any of you .
You two are on your own .
Now we know what we have in common .
Amanda , please . I didn 't know .
Hey , kid ! Amanda !
Where are you ?
Please don 't leave me .
We gotta move .
Hey , kid !
Amanda !
I found a way out .
Eight .
Hey , kid !
Do not run .
Eric . Eric .
No ! Stop !
Get off of me !
We tried it your way .
You motherfucker ! Where is he ?
Eric .
Damn it .
I 'd like to go now until your son is pissing blood .
Now , that 's the Eric Matthews they gave medals to .
Help !
Help me !
Oh , my God .
Jonas .
Help me ! Help me !
Help !
Please .
It 's okay .
- Help me . - It 's okay .
No . No .
No !
Fucker !
Amanda .
Nobody 's listening anymore , asshole .
Open your mouth . Open your mouth ! Come on .
There you go .
You gonna tell me where he is now , huh ?
What ?
Say it again .
Game over .
I 'll take you to the house .
You 're gonna take me right now . Right now .
I will only take you .
No one else .
All right . Just me and you .
- How do we get out of here ? - There 's a button on the wall .
You 'd better hurry .
There 's not much time left .
- The elevator ! - Come on !
Fuck !
Secure the warehouse now !
- All right , let 's go ! Go ! Go , go , go ! - Damn it .
We 've got a lock .
This is Kerry . They 're both gone .
If I don 't find my son , I swear to God ...
Kerry , they 're gone .
Fucking gone .
Yes ! Kerry . We got a lock . We got a lock on the house .
- Rigg , we got it . - What ?
237 North Hyde Crescent .
- That 's North Hyde Crescent . - 237 North Hyde Crescent . Got it .
Where to now ?
Straight ahead .
Come on , come on . Where are you ?
Make a right on Alfred .
Open the fucking door !
Open the door !
There 's nowhere to go .
All I want is the number on the back of your head .
There 's nowhere to go ! Come on , Amanda !
I can 't hold it .
Come on ! Let me in !
Let me in !
Open the door ! Come on !
What do we do ?
Take a left at the next street .
It 's the last house on the left .
Oh , shit .
Shit !
Come on !
Come on , Amanda !
- Amanda , what is it ? - It 's a door .
It 's a fucking door .
You have nowhere to go ! You have nowhere to go !
Come on !
Help me move this thing .
I 'm not gonna hurt you .
Come on , Amanda !
Shit , it 's locked !
Let me in !
Come on , open the door !
Come on !
The key . The one we found with the tape recorder .
Where is it ? Where is it ?
Fuck !
Jonas . Jonas had it last .
- Come on , Amanda ! - Find it ! Hurry !
Come on !
Come on , open the door !
Let me in !
Eric , you 're gonna need this key when you get inside the house .
Where the hell are we ?
Run ! Run !
Daniel ?
Daniel !
Daniel , we gotta go !
- We gotta go ! Come on ! - Run .
All right , come on . Let 's go . Let 's go . Let 's go .
Let 's go , let 's go , let 's go !
Go , go , go !
- Hallway 's clear . - We 're in .
Daniel !
- The ground floor is secure . - Moving up . Moving up .
Kerry , we 're in the house . I repeat , we 're in the house .
Cannot see you , Sergeant . Repeat , cannot see you .
Repeat . I cannot see you .
- Where the hell is everybody ? - What is your 20 ?
Rigg , do you copy ?
Hello , Mr. Hindle .
Follow your heart .
I really wish I had checked in there first .
What the fuck is this ?
My name is very fucking confused . What 's your name ?
I 'm gonna kill your husband now , Mrs. Gordon .
He doesn 't want us to cut through our chains .
What are you doing to me ? No !
He wants us to cut through our feet .
No ! Oh , my God !
It hurts !
No !
Daniel !
Daniel , no . Don 't leave me .
Please .
He 's gone .
Doesn 't matter .
All I want is the number on the back of his neck .
And then yours .
You still don 't know your own number .
How are you gonna get it if I don 't tell you ?
Daniel !
Shit .
Run !
Fuck .
Daniel ?
I still cannot see you , Sergeant .
Rigg , do you copy ?
- Left side clear . - Right side clear .
All clear .
I still can 't see you , Sergeant . I repeat , cannot see you .
It 's not live .
Kerry , we 're in the wrong fucking house !
They 've been dead this whole fucking time .
- Get your team out of there . - Let 's go .
Daniel ?
Daniel .
Hello , Eric . You probably don 't even remember me ,
but you changed my life once .
You sent me to prison .
I was guilty of a lot of things ,
but not the drug charge you framed me for .
You wouldn 't know the things you lose when you 're locked away .
The second time somebody changed my life , I was guilty .
Hello , Amanda .
But my life was saved that day .
- You said you survived this , right ? - Yeah .
I found myself a father , a leader , a teacher .
You must meet death
in order to be reborn .
He helped me .
What is the cure for cancer , Eric ?
Those who don 't appreciate life do not deserve life .
The cure for death itself ?
The answer is immortality .
Daniel !
By creating a legacy ,
by living a life worth remembering , you become immortal .
So now you find the tables are turned .
He asked for you .
- What the fuck do you want ? - I told you .
He wants us to survive this .
I want to play a game .
You have to play by the fucking rules !
The rules are simple .
All you have to do is sit here and talk to me .
What ?
If you can do that long enough , you will find your son
in a safe and secure state .
What the fuck is that ?
It 's your son , Daniel . You remember him , don 't you ?
My dad 's a ...
He 's a real hardass .
I call you unworthy
of the life that you 've been given .
The knowledge of your son 's impending death
has caused you to forgive all his sins .
Why is that we 're only willing to do that when a life is at stake ?
Daniel !
I 'm done listening to you .
Don 't forget the rules .
Shut the fuck up !
He 's playing a game .
I don 't wanna talk to him .
You 're not saying shit .
We both know the sort of person you are .
I 'd like to go now until your son is pissing ...
I 'll take you to the house .
Daniel ?
There 's something I haven 't told you , Eric .
It is I who will carry on John 's work after he dies .
Daniel !
So go ahead . Destroy it .
And you ...
Daniel !
... are my first test subject .
Now you are locked away ,
helpless and alone .
- You fucking bitch . - Game over .
I 'll fucking kill you !
You fucking bitch !
No !
- Subpack by nmkmac -